Love is timeless
A Biltmore Christmas is a romance, fantasy, tv
movie film directed by John Putch.
Contemporary screenwriter Lucy Hardgrove is hired to pen the remake of the holiday
classic His Merry Wife!, which was shot at the renowned Biltmore Estate.
Taking a tour of the grounds, she accidentally knocks over an hourglass,
transporting her back in time to 1946, right when His Merry Wife!
is being filmed.
Lucy Hardgrove, played by Bethany Joy Lenz.
Jack Huston, played by Kristoffer Polaha.
Claude Lancaster, played by Colton Little.
Margaret, played by A.K. Benninghofen.
Ava Hayward, played by Annabelle Borke.
Peggy, played by Jennifer Cortese.
Biltmore Estate is a historic house museum and tourist
attraction in Asheville, North Carolina.
The main residence is the Biltmore House (or Biltmore Mansion), a Châteauesque-style
mansion built for George Washington Vanderbilt II between 1889 and 1895.
It is the largest privately owned house in the United States at 178,926 sq ft
(16,622.8 m2) of floor space and 135,280 sq ft (12,568 m2) of living area.
It is still owned by George Vanderbilt's descendants and remains one
of the most prominent examples of Gilded Age mansions.
The film explores themes of holiday, screenwriter,
time travel, north carolina, hourglass.
The tone is emotional.